http://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/privacy.asp

Link To This Page
Visit MND at MBA in NYC!
1,829# of Questions Answered
Premium Services
MBS Live!
Cobranding Services
NO COMPETITOR ADS!!
VIDEO
MND Live!
MORTGAGE RATES
Subscribe (free)
News and Blogs
Q&A (wiki)
Effective and Last Updated: August 1, 2010
This website is owned and operated by Brown House Media, Inc.
We are committed to protecting the
privacy of our visitors while they interact with the content, products and services on this site
(the “Site”).
This Privacy Policy applies to the Site only. It does not apply to other websites to which we
link.
BecaIf you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.
Occasionally we may revise this Privacy Policy. If we make revisions that change the way we collect
information, those changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the
beginning of the Policy. You should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current
policies and practices.
Information Collected
We collect two types of information from you: i) information that you voluntarily provide to us (e.g.
through a voluntary registration process, sign-ups or emails); and ii) information that is derived through
automated tracking mechanisms.
Voluntary Registration Information
In order to fully access all features of this Site, you must first complete the registration process,
during which we will collect personally identifiable information about you. The information may include your
name, address, telephone number and email address. We do not collect personally identifiable information
about you except when you specifically provide such information to us on a voluntary basis.
By registering with us, you consent to the use and method of disclosure as described in this Privacy
Policy.
Voluntary Information for Services and Features
We [also] collect personally identifiable information when you choose to use certain other features of the
Site, including: purchasing subscriptions, email news alerts, text alerts, Q&A question and answer
submissions, email forwards, inviting friends, participating in our forums, rating/tagging/commenting
articles/posts/pages, surveys, creating a profile, contacting us, submitting loan scenarios and loan
closings, and others.
When you choose to use these additional features, we require you to provide your
“Contact Information” in addition to other personal information that may be required to complete a
transaction such as your phone number, billing and shipping addresses and credit card information.
Cookies
Our site uses "cookies" and other tracking technologies.
Cookies enable us to serve secure pages to our
users without asking them to sign in repeatedly.
Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including
whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. If a user's system is idle for a defined time, the
cookie will expire, forcing the user to sign in again to continue their session. This prevents unauthorized
access to the user's information while they are away from their computer.
You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with
your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter
your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Site.
Third-Party Cookies:
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers
may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by
this site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers See "Third Party Advertisers."
Clear Gifs (Web Beacons)
We employ a software technology called clear gifs. Clear gifs are often referred to as pixel tags or Web
Beacons. These clear gifs are used to help us recognize and assess traffic patterns on our website. Clear
gifs are actually small graphics that contain a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are
used to track the online movements of Web users. Unlike cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard
drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly into Web pages. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs
to our user's personally identifiable information.
Third Party Advertisers
Some of the advertisements appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by third party advertisers.
We may share Web site usage information about users with reputable third parties for the purpose of targeting
our advertisements on this site.
Third party advertisers may uses cookies and clear GIFs on this site, which allow it to recognize a user's
cookie when a user visits this site. The collected and shared through this technology is not personally
identifiable.
If you would like more information about this practice or to opt out of having this information used by
companies that are part of the Network Advertising Initiative to provide targeted ads, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp.
Notice
Third Party Web Sites
Our web site links to web sites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-
branded or provide data/services.
We're not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to
or integrated with our sites or for the privacy practices of third party Internet advertising companies. Once
you've left our site via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable
privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any PII they collect
from you.
Links to Other Sites
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Brown House Media, Inc.
Please be aware that we, Brown House Media, Inc., are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other
sites.
We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every
Web site that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.
How We Use Your Information
Mortgage News Daily only uses your personal information for the original purposes it was given.
Your personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third
parties without your approval at the time of collection.
Mortgage News Daily will not disclose, use, give or sell any personal information to third parties for any
purposes other than to our suppliers and other third parties who need to know in order to deliver services on
behalf of Mortgage News Daily unless required to do so by law. Further, Mortgage News Daily reserves the
right to contact you regarding matters relevant to the underlying service provided and/or the information
collected.
Please note that personally identifiable information is used only to provide you with a more enjoyable,
convenient online experience and to help us identify and/or provide information, products or services that
may be of interest to you. We use your personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of
the Site and its features.
Mortgage News Daily may use your personal information for target advertising toward you based on things
such as location, region, gender, interests, goals, habits, etc.
We may permit certain trusted third parties to track usage, analyze data such as the source address that a
page request is coming from, your IP address or domain name, the date and time of the page request, the
referring Web site (if any) and other parameters in the URL. This is collected in order to better understand
our Web site usage, and enhance the performance of services to maintain and operate the Site and certain
features on the Site. We may use third parties to host the Site; operate various features available on the
Site; send emails; analyze data; provide search results and links and assist in fulfilling your orders.
Also, we may share personally identifiable or other information with our parent, subsidiaries, divisions,
and affiliates.
We may transfer personally identifiable information as an asset in connection with a proposed or actual
merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all
or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in control.
Mortgage News Daily may disclose Contact Information in special cases where we have reason to believe that
disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may
be violating our terms and conditions of use or may be causing injury or interference with our rights,
property, our customers or anyone who could be harmed by such activities.
WE ARE NOT LIABLE OR RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE OR OTHER INFORMATION YOU CHOOSE TO SUBMIT
IN FORUMS SUCH AS A BULLETIN BOARD, CHAT ROOM, COMMENTS OR ANY OTHER PUBLICLY ACCESSIBLE AREA OF THE
SITE.
You will receive notice when your personally identifiable information might be provided to any third party
for any reason other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, and you will have an opportunity to request
that we not share such information.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and for business and
administrative purposes. We may also use or share with third parties for any purpose aggregated data that
contains no personally identifiable information.
How We Protect Your Information
We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We take appropriate security measures
to protect your information against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or
destruction of data. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of
information, we maintain appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure
the information and data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the
measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of
data involved.
Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information and Preferences
We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personal information for many of our services.
You
may modify or remove any of your personal information at any time by logging into your account and accessing
features such as edit and account.
Email Choice/Opt-out
If you no longer wish to receive updates or notifications may opt-out of receiving these communications by
changing your “email notification” settings in your “account settings.”
Children's Privacy and Parental Controls
We do not solicit any personal information from children. If you are not 18 or older, you are not
authorized to use the Site. Parents should be aware that there are parental control tools available online
that can be used to prevent children from submitting information online without parental permission or from
accessing material that is harmful to minors.
Disclaimer to Security
By consenting to the Terms and Conditions of the Site and hence the Privacy Policy, you consent that no
data transmission over the Internet is completely secure. We cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any
information you provide to us and you transmit such information to us at your own risk.
Business Transitions
In the event BROWN HOUSE MEDIA, INC. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by
another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will
likely be among the assets transferred.
Legal Disclaimer
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we
believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court
order, or legal process served on our Web site.
Data Retention
We retain your information for as long as necessary to permit us to use it for the purposes that we have
communicated to you and comply with applicable law or regulations.
Notification of Changes
Mortgage News Daily reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole
discretion. If at some point in the future, there is a change to our Privacy Policy, unless we obtain your
express consent, such change will only apply to information collected after the revised Privacy Policy took
effect. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted.
CONTACT INFORMATION:
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy please contact:
Mortgage News Daily
Attn: Privacy Policy
19706 One Norman Blvd. - Suite B225
Cornelius, NC 28031
http://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com
Contact us online
FREE MEMBERSHIP
Membership Advantages
Register for Free
Sign In
Forgot Password
MBS LIVE!
Learn About MBS Live!
2 Week Free Trial
Sign In
MORE INFO
Contact Us
Advertising
Become a Contributor
About MND
NEWS
MBS Prices
MBS Live!
Housing Data
MARKETPLACE
Local Mortgage Professionals
Local Real Estate Professionals
+Add Your Free Listing
Vendor Marketplace
Browse Companies
+Add Your Company
Our Story
Founded in 2004, Mortgage News Daily has established itself as a leader in housing news, analysis and data.
Our innovative social media platform combines industry leading content and data with an active community of industry professionals, to accomplish our primary goal - keeping our readers informed.
Total Members
189,509
Subscribe to Our Newsletter
Follow On Your Mobile Device
Subscribe To RSS
Follow On Twitter
Follow On Facebook
Home -
RSS
All Content Copyright © 2003 - 2020 Brown House Media, Inc. All Rights Reserved.Reproduction in whole or in part in any form without the express written permission of MortgageNewsDaily.com is prohibited.
